♪ Search on the power line, remember goodbye ♪
Speaking of the creation hell in my day
A romantic speech-wise, a human set, all-
♪ Up on a road that lets begin the simulation ♪
(upbeat music)
With fun, set up once, then I will give you more
I'll give you my separate if I'm as ugly as you are.
♪ If you can say it all on my hand ♪
♪ I just fight for training ♪
Infinity, then you can be more than a tiger
The end of my mind vision, so they'll see
So busy, the living can travel.
You waited to be seen
Where can you?
You make sure the things are the way.
I can live, I can live in your office, I can live
♪ The sun is watching me, I can't wait to help you ♪
♪ You are my best ♪
♪ So you should never show ♪
♪ I do this for you so you say you love me ♪
I'm the make-one tonight I gave you mine
I'm just crying with a makeover then my love can be...
♪ You can't be extension ♪
♪ I'm gonna tell you can't stay ♪
Bye for you and come in and if I'm done with you
♪ I'm caught in the proof of my existence ♪
♪ That's it ♪
♪ I'm going ginger to love to love you ♪
And do whatever you want.
♪ The end of the search, my role ♪
♪ Do it ♪
♪ Last two times I've been hit in turn ♪
The Trains, the Trains, oh my god!
I can dance, I can steal your vibration
♪ I'm saying like it, man, like it finally ♪
Come on, I'm cold, I'm cold, I'm cold, I'm cold, I'm cold
Too much work, too much love, too much love
You have to put the truth of your situation in my head.
Can you hear me? Can you hear me? So be an understatement!
♪ Zoom baby, baby, baby, you go in the show ♪
This all began linking our thought.
♪ We're in good hands ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Except you, except you, except you, except you, except you ♪
♪ Such a human, such a human, such a human ♪
♪ Such a human, such a human ♪
You can accept your hand, accept your hand, accept your hand
It makes a new human mind, but it's quite me.
I can't get no more of the execution of it.
♪ I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't ♪
♪ So move, move, move, move, move, move, move ♪
Don't know what I'm saying, baby!
♪ You've already told your brother you ♪
♪ I'm out of my class ♪
Can you ask me, I can't answer all of that?
I'm all in love to watch it break
It's passion
♪ You'll check the fire ♪
♪ I know you are free ♪
♪ I'm catching up ♪
(upbeat music)